

Simon Verhoek

DEVELOPER OF YOUR DREAMS

website phone email address www.simonverhoek.com +31 6 57591310 saverhoek@gmail.com Haarweg 175 509 6709RG Wageningen (NL)

Profile

Hi. My name is Simon. I am a fresh thinker with a passion for HCI, enhancing productivity and coming up with creative and elegant solutions for all of our everyday problems. As a multidisciplinary M.Sc. student with excellent communication skills, I speak the language of many professions. My background covers the fields of software development, functional design, business-IT alignment, consumer behaviour, marketing and sales. My ambition is to take part in the design and development of today's brilliant ideas, so we can simplify our lives tomorrow.

Skills

Programming skills	 Full stack development of web applications in PHP, according to MVC principles Backend: designing mySQL databases for web applications Front end: (functional) design of of websites and web applications with HTML & CSS, JavaScript, jQuery and the Bootstrap framework Experienced in source control management with Git & GitHub Basic programming skills in C & Python 	
Analytical skills	Ability to focus on both oversight and smallest detailsExcellent conceptual definition	
Communicative skills	 Speaking the language of multiple disciplines and bringing them all together Experienced in teamwork and leading teams 	
Creative skills	Encouraging and inspiring people with infectious enthusiasmLoud thinker & unstoppable idea generatorResourceful	
Sales skills	 2+ years experience in persuading and closing deals Skilled in analyzing pain points and Points Of Sale (POS) Intrinsically motivated to help customers 	
Other computer skills	 Building and repairing PCs Experienced in troubleshooting & end user support Configuring home networks, setting up file/media servers, managing ip addresses 	

Education

Ms.c. study 2013	University of Amsterdam (NL)	Information Studies - Business Information Systems Subjects: - Business & IT alignment - Organizational role of modern ICT	
Minor 2014	University of Amsterdam (NL)	Programming Subjects: - Basic computer science concepts - Designing software applications - Programming (C, HTML, CSS, PHP, SQL, Python)	
Masterclass/ traineeship 2012 - 2013	Professional Capital (NL)	Sales & Account Management Subjects: - Honing professional sales & account management skills of commercial talents	
B.Sc. study 2008 - 2012	Wageningen University (NL)	Management & Consumer Studies Subjects: - Consumers' ways of thinking and buying decisions - Exploiting above knowledge in marketing & sales	
High school 2002 - 2008	Pentum College C.S.G. Jacob van Liesveldt (NL)	 vwo - bilingual (English) profile: Economics & Society International Baccalaureate (Native Speaker in English) Extra courses: Informatics, Management&Organization 	

Experience

TEMPORARY CUSTOMER SERVICE EMPLOYEE, PORTAAL (NL) – 2013

Arranging appointments by phone with tenants for a routine control project and taking care of the organization and administration around this project.

ON-FLOOR ICT SUPPORT, NATIONALE NEDERLANDEN (NL) – 2013

Providing first-line ICT support on the work floor during a company-wide domain migration.

TRAINEE JUNIOR ACCOUNT MANAGER, RACKTIME (NL) – 2012-2013

300 hours of internship at field marketing services provider Racktime BV. My tasks consisted of:

- gaining selling experience in various B2C sales projects
- visiting shops and taking care of product presentation
- negotiating with shop managers about shelf space for products and merchandise

TELEPHONE SALES AGENT, ANNIE CONNECT (NL) - 2009 - 2010

Selling lottery tickets by phone for a Dutch lottery, and receiving calls for various charity projects.

Interests

Programming, fiddling with computers, DJing, collecting electronic music, snowboarding